ABHISHITH KOMBATH

■ Abhishithdasan01@gmail.com \$\square\$ 9821654160

SUMMARY

Disciplined and insightful MIS Executive with over 8.10 years of professional experience. Keen to support TechMahindra with excellent organizational and analytical skills. At Teleperformance DIBS Private Limited helped increase process service level and improve adherence which saved 200K a year by redesigning template to track production compared to adherence. And have also automated reports which help reduce report preparation time increasing report accuracy.

EDUCATION

Bharathiar University
MBA International Business 2020

26 1 127 1 1 1

Madurai Kamaraj university 2013 - 2016

Bsc Maths 2016

EMPLOYMENT

Teleperformance DIBS, WFM/MIS Executive, Mumbai

June 2017 - Current

- Create process template and automate reports
- Provide daily/intraday performance reports to leadership
- · Analyzes reports to make recommendations for adjusting staffing levels to meet departmental productivity and profitability goals
- Track time and attendance to process and reveal attendance and schedule patterns to help manage shrinkage and adherence of the process.
- · Prepare and distribute daily, monthly and quarterly report on matrices related to site performance
- · Track break moments on the floor to ensure process adherence are met on interval basis

Senior Customer Service Representative, Mumbai

Apr. 2015 - May 2017

- Submitted detailed claims to insurance companies for health care providers
- Reviewed patient bills for accuracy and completeness, and obtained any missing information
- Maintain highest levels of accuracy and patient confidentiality
- · Trained new joiners and helped them understand process and achieve goals based on production requirement

Dish Hospitality (Nido Restaurant), Trainee Assistant Steward, Mumbai

Aug. 2013 - Sept. 2014

- · Assisted guests to tables and managed resetting schedule as per requirement
- Maintained all equipment's and materials as per appropriate handling procedures
- Monitored all dispensing machines and performed regular sanitization of line
- Administered collection and storage of various restaurant supplies
- Ensured optimal level of guest services for all food and beverage services

SKILLS

Excel, Python

PROJECTS

Food ordering app

Dec. 2021 - Dec. 2021

- Register user and save credentials
- Display menu to customers and also give admin the access to edit the menu
- Take orders based on customer input
- Save orders and display order history when requested
- · Maintain revenue details

AWARDS

Best Performer Q1 Apr. 2018